play-asia.com 2005-08-30

# Play-Asia.com - Japanese & Asian Video Games for Consoles and PC

|   
---|---  
  
  |  |    
  
|  | 

Location: Play-Asia.com Privacy Statement  
  
---|---|---  
  
|   
---  
|  |   |   
  |  **Privacy Statement**   

> Play-Asia.com knows that you care how information about you is used and shared, and we appreciate your trust that we will do so carefully and sensibly. This notice describes our privacy policy. By visiting Play-Asia.com, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Statement.

What Personal Information About Customers Does Play-Asia.com Gather?  

> The information we learn from customers helps us personalize and continually improve your shopping experience at Play-Asia.com. Here are the types of information we gather.
> 
> Information You Give Us: We receive and store any information you enter on our Web site or give us in any other way. Those include your personal details you enter when creating a customer account as well as product pages you are visiting and E-Mail subscriptions you are making. We use the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, customizing future shopping for you, improving our store, and communicating with you.
> 
> Automatic Information: We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. For example, like many Web sites, we use "cookies," and we obtain certain types of information when your Web browser accesses Play-Asia.com, such as your IP address, your web browser type, operating system, URL clickstreams and similar. A number of companies offer utilities designed to help you visit Web sites anonymously. Although we will not be able to provide you with a personalized experience at Play-Asia.com if we cannot recognize you, we want you to be aware that these tools exist.
> 
> Information from Other Sources: We might receive information about you from other sources and add it to our account information. Those include for example updated delivery and address information from our carriers or other third parties, which we use to correct our records and deliver your next purchase or communication more easily; account information, purchase or redemption information, and page-view information from some merchants with which we operate co-branded businesses or for which we provide technical, fulfillment, advertising, or other services.

What About Cookies?  

> Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and to provide cerain features for you, such as automatic login, product recommendations and else.
> 
> The Help portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. However, cookies allow you to take full advantage of some of Play-Asia.com's coolest features, and we recommend that you leave them turned on.

Does Play-Asia.com Share the Information It Receives?  

> Information about our customers is an important part of our business, and we are not in the business of selling it to others. We share customer information only in the events as described below:
> 
>   1. Agents: We employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples may include fulfilling orders, delivering packages, sending postal mail and E-Mail, removing repetitive information from customer lists, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, processing credit card payments, and providing customer service. They have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes.
>   2. Business Transfers: As we continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy stores, subsidiaries, or business units. In such transactions, customer information generally is one of the transferred business assets but remains subject to the promises made in any pre-existing Privacy Notice. Also, in the unlikely event that Play-Asia.com., or substantially all of its assets are acquired, customer information will of course be one of the transferred assets.
>   3. Protection of Play-Asia.com and Others: We release account and other personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law; enforce or apply our Terms of Use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of Play-Asia.com, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction. Obviously, however, this does not include selling, renting, sharing, or otherwise disclosing personally identifiable information from customers for commercial purposes in violation of the commitments set forth in this Privacy Statement.
>   4. With Your Consent: Other than as set out above, you will receive notice when information about you might go to third parties, and you will have an opportunity to choose not to share the information.
> 

How Secure Is Information About Me?  

> We work to protect the security of your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input.
> 
> It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to logoff when finished using a shared computer. Click here for more information on how to .

What Choices Do I Have?  

> As discussed above, you can always choose not to provide certain information, even though it might be needed to make a purchase or to take advantage of such Play-Asia.com features.
> 
> You can add or update certain information in your "My Account". When you update information, we usually keep a copy of the prior version for our records.
> 
> The Help portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. However, you will not be able to use certain important features if you do not use cookies.

Children  

> Play-Asia.com does not sell products for purchase by children. We sell children's products for purchase by adults. If you are under 18, you may use Play-Asia.com only with the involvement of a parent or guardian.

Conditions of Use, Notices, and Revisions  

> If you choose to visit Play-Asia.com, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Notice and our Terms of Use, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of the law of the HKSAR.
> 
> Our business changes constantly, and our Privacy Statement and the Terms of Use will change also. We may e-mail periodic reminders of our notices and conditions, but you should check our Web site frequently to see recent changes. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Statement applies to all information that we have about you and your account. We stand behind the promises we make, however, and will never materially change our policies and practices to make them less protective of customer information collected in the past without the consent of affected customers.

|   
  |  |    
  |    
|   |    
   
|   new releases  
---  
  
|    | Zwei !! (Taito the Best) |  US$ 34.90  

or   
save for later  
---|---|---  
Falcom  
Compatible with PlayStation2™  
Japanese, NTSC J / RPG  
Usually ships within 24hrs  
   
   | Namco Museum Battle Collection |  US$ 49.90  

or   
save for later  
Namco  
Compatible with Sony PSP™  
US, No Region Protection / Classics  
Usually ships within 24hrs  
   
   | From TV Animation: One Piece Grand Battle: Combat Rush |  US$ 59.90  

or   
save for later  
Bandai  
Compatible with PlayStation2™  
Korean, NTSC J / Action Adventure  
Usually ships within 1 to 2 weeks  
   
   | Heavy Metal Thunder |  US$ 59.90  

or   
save for later  
Square Enix  
Compatible with PlayStation2™  
Asia, NTSC J / Action  
Usually ships within 24hrs  
   
   | Bleach: Heat the Soul 2 |  US$ 49.90  

or   
save for later  
Sony Computer Entertainment  
Compatible with Sony PSP™  
Asia, No Region Protection / Fighting  
Usually ships within 24hrs  
   
   | Pac'n Roll DS |  US$ 39.90  

or   
save for later  
Namco  
Compatible with Nintendo DS™  
US, No Region Protection / Action  
Usually ships within 24hrs  
   
   | [Koukyoushihen Eureka Seven Vol.2 [DVD+UMD]](https://web.archive.org/paOS-13-71-bb-70-rw3.html) |  US$ 77.90  

or   
save for later  
Bandai  
Compatible with Sony PSP™  
Japanese, UMD Video (RC2/Japan) / Animation  
Usually ships within 5-15 days  
   
   | Initial D UMD Box Set (w/ Initial D PSP™ Carrying Bag) |  US$ 29.90  

or   
save for later  
Media Asia  
Compatible with Sony PSP™  
Hong Kong, UMD Video (RC3/Asia) / Action  
Jay Chow, Anthony Wong, ...  
Usually ships within 24hrs  

discounted items 

   | Virtua Fighter Cyber Generation: Ambition of the Judgement Six |  US$ 19.90  

or   
save for later  
---|---|---  
Sega  
Compatible with Gamecube™  
Japanese, NTSC J / RPG  
Usually ships within 24hrs  
   
   | Sherlock Holmes Consulting Detective (CD-ROM²) |  US$ 19.90  

or   
save for later  
Victor  
Compatible with PC-Engine™  
Japanese, NTSC J / Adventure  
Usually ships within 24hrs  
   
   | Baseball |  US$ 14.90  

or   
save for later  
Nintendo of Japan  
Compatible with Game Boy™  
Japanese, No Region Protection / Sports  
Usually ships within 24hrs  
   
   | Pokemon Box Ruby & Sapphire |  US$ 9.90  

or   
save for later  
Nintendo of Japan  
Compatible with Gamecube™  
Japanese, NTSC J / Misc  
Usually ships within 24hrs  
   
   | Everblue (CapKore) |  US$ 8.90  

or   
save for later  
Capcom  
Compatible with PlayStation2™  
Japanese, NTSC J / Action Adventure  
Usually ships within 24hrs  
   
   | Groove Adventure Rave |  US$ 29.90  

or   
save for later  
Konami  
Compatible with PlayStation™  
Japanese, NTSC J / RPG  
Usually ships within 24hrs  
   
   | Super Bomberman: Panic Bomber W |  US$ 12.90  

or   
save for later  
Hudson  
Compatible with Super Famicom™  
Japanese, NTSC J / Puzzle  
Usually ships within 24hrs  
   
   | Kuru Kururin Paradise |  US$ 19.90  

or   
save for later  
Nintendo of Japan  
Compatible with Game Boy Advance™  
Japanese, No Region Protection / Puzzle  
Usually ships within 24hrs  
   
   | DDR Festival Dance Dance Revolution Controller Set |  US$ 69.90  

or   
save for later  
Konami  
Compatible with PlayStation2™  
Japanese, NTSC J / Music  
Usually ships within 24hrs  
   
   | Sentou Yousei Yuki Kaze |  US$ 39.90  

or   
save for later  
Aqua System  
Compatible with Xbox™  
Japanese, NTSC J / Simulation  
Usually ships within 24hrs  
   
   | RockMan X8 (w/ MegaMan X6 for PlayStation™) |  US$ 29.90  

or   
save for later  
Capcom  
Compatible with PlayStation2™  
Korean, NTSC J / Action  
Usually ships within 24hrs  
   
   | [Yu-Gi-Oh Duel Monsters Expert 3 [Beginners Pack] [pre-owned]](https://web.archive.org/paOS-13-71-99-70-hz8.html) |  US$ 39.90  

or   
save for later  
Konami  
Compatible with Game Boy Advance™  
Japanese, No Region Protection / RPG  
Usually ships within 24hrs  
  
Browse more discounted items...  

| Display language:  | English -  | Français -  | Deutsch -  |    
---|---|---|---|---  
Reference currency:  |   
  
Trademarks listed on our pages belong to their designated owner(s). If you have any matter you want to bring up to us regarding copyright or trademarks, please feel free to contact us.  
  
---  
  
Website & content copyright 2002-2005 Play-Asia.com.   
   
Add one of our banners to your site
